http://www.optom.com/privacy-and-security

Call Us
Give the Gift Of Sight!! Ask us about gift certificates!
Whether you're purchasing online or just browsing, your privacy is important to us. Please take the time to review our policy for handling your customer information. By visiting the our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please revisit this page and review the Policy regularly. If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us. We appreciate your comments and suggestions.We may share the information we collect with third parties, as detailed below. We may use the information to improve the content of our website, to make our future marketing efforts more efficient, to notify you about current products, special offers, services and events, and for other purposes. The information we collect may be combined with other personally identifiable information available from our records and other sources, such as purchase history and demographic information.Your trust and privacy are very important to us! Therefore, we ask only for the information we need to process your requests:Postal Address:If you purchase from us or request a catalog by mail, we will need a postal address, and we will add your name to our mailing list. Occasionally, we may also share your name with select companies whose services or products are similar to ours. If you do not want to receive our catalog by mail or do not want your name shared with other companies, just let us know.Phone Number:We ask for your phone number on the order form in the event we need to contact you regarding your order. We will not otherwise call you, and we will not share your phone number with any other companies.Credit Card Information:To purchase from the our website, you will need to give us a credit card number. This information is kept encrypted to ensure secure purchases. This is secure information and cannot be accessed by anyone other than the account holder.E-Mail Address:We will use the e-mail address you provide on your order to send you an order receipt and to communicate about your order. We may also use it to contact you about future website or product updates. Please be assured that the e-mail address you provide to us is for internal use only. If you decide you would like to be removed from this service, you may follow the instructions on the messages you are sent.Questions and Comments:We want to hear from you -- your comments, suggestions, questions. Every message is read and a response sent as quickly as possible if requested. The information you send us is used to respond to your questions and comments only.Cookies:We may also use "cookies" or other means to passively collect information about your use of our website. A cookie is a piece of data stored on your computer that lets your web browser talk with our web server. It saves you from retyping your user name and password every time you use our secure checkout. If you are shopping on our site and are having difficulty completing your order, please check the privacy settings in your browser. If you have your settings set to not accept cookies, you will not be able to purchase from our site.Children:Our website is intended only for those aged 13 and older. If you are under 13, you may not register or submit personally identifiable information on, to or through the site. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we know to be under 13.Opting Out:If you do not wish to receive mailed or emailed promotional material, or if you do not wish your name to be shared with third parties for marketing purposes, please contact us.Security:We take care to protect the security of your personal information, including your credit card information, from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure. However, transmissions to the website may be intercepted and read by others and we cannot be responsible for any such interception.We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your personal on-line order information. To check the security of your connection to our website, look in the lower right-hand corner of your browser window after entering our checkout section. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then SSL is active. On newer versions of some browsing software it may be located in the upper address bar. You can also double-check you are in a secure shopping environment by looking at the URL line of your browser. When you are using a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https." If you cannot access the secure server for any reason, please call and place your order by phone.TERMS OF USEBY USING THIS WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO FOLLOW AND BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS, YOU MAY NOT USE THE SITE.Changes to TermPlease read these Terms regularly, as they may change at any time. By using the Site after a change in the Terms, you agree to follow and be bound by the Terms as changed.Site Content:Everything you see, hear or receive from or on the Site ("Content") is copyright, trademark, trade dress or other intellectual property owned by our company or our licensors. Content includes, without limitation, images, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, trademarks, logos, text, software, sounds and the Site as a whole. You may use or download Content solely for your personal, noncommercial purposes, provided you keep unchanged all copyright and other notices. No other use of Content is permitted. Except for this limited license, nothing in the Terms transfers to you any right, title or interest in any Content. We may change, suspend, restrict or discontinue any aspect of the Site at any time, including any Site feature, service or Content.Comments and Submissions:We welcome your comments regarding our Site, our products and our services. However, any information you transmit to the Site is not, and will not be treated as, private, confidential or proprietary. We may make unrestricted use of any information you transmit to us through the Site. This may include personal information about you and your use of the Site. Please review our Privacy Policy for more information.Use of the Site:You promise to make only lawful use of the Site. You promise to make no use of the Site that violates anyone else's rights, including copyright, trademark, trade secret, privacy or other rights. You promise not to upload, post, transmit, distribute or otherwise publish on or to the Site any materials that (a) contain a software virus or other harmful component, (b) contain advertising or commercial material, or (c) are false, threatening, libelous, defamatory, pornographic, obscene or otherwise unlawful. You are solely responsible for the content of any material you publish on the Site. We are not responsible or liable for the conduct of any Site user, or for materials published to the Site by any Site user other than our company.You may not: (a) use spiders, robots, avatars, intelligent agents or other automated data mining techniques to extract, copy, download, store, reproduce, distribute or post Content; (b) interfere with the Site or any other user's use of the Site, including, without limitation, overloading, "flooding", "mailbombing" or "crashing" the Site; (c) send unsolicited e-mail through the Site or forge or mask your identity in any e-mail or posting; (e) decompile, reverse engineer or disassemble any software or other products or processes accessible through the Site, or (e) insert any code or product or manipulate the Content in any way that affects any user's experience of the Site.Information:Prices are valid only in the United States. Prices are subject to change without notice. We try to accurately display the colors of our products on the Site. However, the colors you see will depend on your monitor and its settings. We cannot guarantee that your display will be accurate. We do not warrant the currency, accuracy or reliability of any Site information, including information about product price or availability.Links to Other Sites:The Site may contain links to third party sites. Any outside links are provided only as a convenience. Your use of outside links is at your sole risk. Links from the Site do not constitute our endorsement of any third party, its website, or its goods or services. We are not responsible for any outside sites, services or other materials linked to or from the Site, and disclaims all liability for any injury you may experience by using such materials.Links to the Site:You may not create hyperlinks to the Site that portray our company in a false or misleading light. You may not use any "framing" or similar techniques to enclose any portion of the Site. You may link only to the front page of the Site, and not to any other pages.Disclaimers:If you are dissatisfied with the Site, any Contents, or any of the Terms, we would like to hear from you. However, your only legal remedy is to stop using the Site.YOUR USE OF THE SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT ALLOWED BY LAW, WE MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND IN CONNECTION WITH THE SITE. WE PROVIDE THIS SITE, ALL CONTENT, AND ALL SERVICES OFFERED THROUGH OR FROM THE SITE "AS IS." WE DISCLAIM ALL EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, QUIET ENJOYMENT, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.WE SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES RELATED TO YOUR USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THIS SITE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, COMPENSATORY OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, LOST PROFITS OR LOSS OF OR DAMAGE TO PROPERTY, EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.Some states do not allow certain limitations on implied warranties or on damages, so some of the above exclusions may not apply to you. We do not warrant that your use of the Site, the operation of the Site, or any services offered on the Site will be uninterrupted or error free, that defects will be corrected, or that the Site is free of viruses or other harmful elements.Indemnification:You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless our company and its officers, directors, owners, agents, employees, affiliates, licensees and licensors from and against any and all claims, damages, costs and expenses, including attorneys' fees, arising from or related to your use of the Site in violation of any of the Terms.Miscellaneous:We display this Site and the Content solely to market and promote our products and services. The Terms shall be construed according to our home sate law, without regard to its conflicts of laws provisions. Any dispute arising under or relating to the Terms, Contents, your use of the Site, or products or services purchased using the Site, shall be resolved exclusively by the state and federal courts of our companies home state. By using the Site, you consent to the jurisdiction and venue of our states courts with respect to any such dispute.If any provision of the Terms, or any portion thereof, is found to be unenforceable, it shall be enforced to the maximum extent permissible so as to effect the intent of the Terms, and the rest of the Terms shall remain in full force and effect.The Terms are the entire agreement between you and our company relating to the Site. These Terms supersede and cancel any prior written or oral agreement between you and our company relating to the Site, which shall have no further force or effect. All rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.Termination:Your failure to comply with the Terms automatically revokes your authorization to use the Site and terminates all rights granted to you under the Terms. Your obligations to our company shall continue upon termination of your rights under the Terms, including restrictions regarding the Content, disclaimers and liability limitations under the Terms. If your rights are terminated, you must promptly destroy all Content obtained from this Site, as well as all copies of Content.
Arena Eyeworks Optometry © 2020
back to top
A Mopro Website
